newspress.co.uk 2009-12-28

# Welcome to Newspress.co.uk

## TERMS & CONDITIONS 

The Newspress website is a media resource service provided by Newspress Ltd. We are registered in England and Wales under company number 01106594 and our main trading address is situated at 6 Newhouse Business Centre, Old Crawley Road, Horsham, West Sussex RH12 4RU. The website has been designed for the purpose of enabling the automotive industry to disseminate press releases and related information to UK media. The Newspress site is a secure site and may contain information that is sensitive and not generally available to the public. Access to this restricted site is at Newspress’s discretion and access will only be provided to accredited motoring journalists, professional news organisations and industry personnel.

Access is subject to the terms and conditions of use as detailed below. By accessing the website, you will be deemed to have accepted the terms in full and agree to abide by them. Newspress may update and revise the terms at any time without notice and you should check the website from time to time to review any amendments as these are legally binding on you.

Access to the site is monitored. The requesting URLs, the machine originating the request and the time of the request are logged for access statistics and security purposes. Use of this website constitutes consent to such monitoring. This website may be unavailable from time to time due to mechanical, telecommunication, software, hardware and third party failures. Newspress Ltd cannot predict or control when such downtime may occur nor control the duration of such downtime.

### User ID

In applying for a user ID you will be asked to provide Newspress Ltd with personal information and you must first agree with the Newspress **privacy policy**. 

Your User ID and password are non-transferable and you must not allow another person to use these details to access the site. By using your ID and password you agree that you will not do anything which would assist anyone who is not a registered user to gain access. If for any reason we believe that you have not complied with these requirements, we may, at our discretion, cancel your access to the Newspress website immediately and without advance notice.

You must not in any way alter the site, or interfere with or affect its working.

Although Newspress makes reasonable efforts to ensure the accuracy and reliability of the information contained on the Newspress website, Newspress will not be held liable in relation to the accuracy of the information or for any loss or damage of any type in connection with the provision of or failure to provide the service. Newspress is not responsible for misprints, out-of-date information, technical or pricing inaccuracies, typographical or other errors appearing on the website.The content and accuracy of press material are wholly the responsibility of the originating company or organisation. All information should be checked prior to publication. Information and related materials are subject to change without notice. By using this website, you assume the risk that the information and materials on this website may be incomplete, inaccurate, out of date, or may not meet your needs and requirements.

Newspress owns or is the licensee of all intellectual property rights on the website and the material published on it, including all design, operating software and graphics. 

The press material provided by third parties is intended for use by journalists in connection with their professional activities and may be viewed, downloaded, reproduced and adapted in both printed and electronic form only for the purpose of providing the public with a reporting service (and not promotional material) in print, broadcast or on-line media, and for no other purpose. Nearly all images are copyright protected for editorial use only and must not be used for marketing, advertising or promotional purposes without the prior written permission of the copyright owner.

Apart from these uses, redistribution, database storage or commercial exploitation of the contents of this site are prohibited without the express permission of Newspress.

Much of the information on this website relates to the UK market. It may be accessed by users internationally but users must note that the information may not be applicable to your market.

Where links to other sites and resources are provided, these are for your information only. We have no control over the content of these sites or resources and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them.

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

Newspress operates a strict privacy policy which provides you with the information on the personal details we collect from you, how we use it and to whom we may disclose such personal information.

We are notified under the UK Data Protection Act with the Information Commissioner.

### **Definitions Used**

a) ‘DPA 1998’ means the Data Protection Act 1998, as amended.

b) ‘personal information’ means any information that we have obtained from you or third parties in connection with a service or product provided to you that is held now or at any time in the future by Newspress Ltd. 

c) ‘Website’ means [www.newspress.co.uk](http://www.newspress.co.uk/).

d) ‘We/us/our’ means Newspress Ltd, company registration number 01106594

### **What personal information do we obtain and process and why?**

a) In order for you to be able to access and use the updating, archive and daily release services provided by the Website, you need to register with us. During the registration process, we shall obtain certain log-in information from you. This information includes your name, contact details and your categories of interest.

b) We use the personal information we obtain from you:

i) to administer your registration to the Website;

ii) for administration and statistical analysis;

iii) to supply you with the press information and services requested by you; and 

iv) to monitor, maintain, administer, enhance or develop the website, which may include disclosing your information to trusted and carefully selected third parties who in turn may contact you to provide press information that they think may be of interest to you (where we do this, your information will be disclosed only for this limited purpose).

c) We would like to contact you from time to time to provide you with information about:

i) Newspress;

ii) Changes to our services that we think may be of interest; and 

iii) The products and services of carefully selected organisations which we think may be of interest (primarily press information).

d) Newspress uses cookies to store and retrieve your login information so you are not required to enter your details every time you visit the site. Information stored on these cookies is not used for any other purpose. If you do not have cookies activated you will need to login each time you visit.

e) Site usage statistics and individual press release usage statistics are provided to our clients in the form of reports. This information does not contain your personal details, simply the number of click throughs and the media type you represent.

f) We may contact you by phone, post or email to supply you with press information. You may opt out of these services and if you wish to stop receiving emails at any time, simply send an e-mail to [newspress@newspress.co.uk](mailto:newspress@newspress.co.uk) and state ‘unsubscribe’.

### Your consent

By registering with us, using the Website and subscribing for services offered through the Website:

a) you accept and agree that certain information about you will be captured electronically or otherwise and transmitted to us and, potentially, to any third parties as set out above.

b) you expressly agree to the collection and use of your personal information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. 

### Refreshing your details

You can update your personal record by sending an email to [click here](mailto:newspress@newspress.co.uk)

### **Sharing of information with third parties**

We follow security procedures as required by the UK Data Protection Act 1998, in the storage and disclosure of personal information that you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access to such information. As mentioned we may let you know about the products or services provided by carefully selected third parties. We endeavour to only deal with partners who comply with the DPA and any other applicable data protection legislation or regulations. However, to the extent permitted by law, we shall have no liability to you in respect of any breach of security by a third party.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to add to or change the terms of this Privacy Policy in our sole discretion, without prior notice to you. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the new Privacy Policy on the Website, and it will become effective from the time of posting to the Website.
